<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on Paavo Niskala</title>
    <link>https://pniskala.github.io/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on Paavo Niskala</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://pniskala.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://pniskala.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 12:01:47 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pniskala.github.io/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Working with Quarto and Hugo</title>
      <link>https://pniskala.github.io/posts/working-with-quarto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 12:01:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pniskala.github.io/posts/working-with-quarto/</guid>
      <description>Quick intro to Quarto While exploring the offerings of Fast.ai, I got introduced to Quarto, a handy-looking open-source publishing system.
In practice, Quarto allows publishing your work – were it code, data analysis, or just plain markdown text – in a variety of formats including PowerPoint, HTML, and so on.
As a practical example I decided to try Quarto out by creating a very quick data exploration notebook as the system has a nice integration with Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning by doing: Setting up a website with Hugo and GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://pniskala.github.io/posts/github_pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 21:43:09 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pniskala.github.io/posts/github_pages/</guid>
      <description>I just set up this website with GitHub Pages and Hugo so why not share that experience on that very website? It only makes sense!
Somewhat irrelevant background information I have tried a variety of blogging platforms (e.g. Wordpress) in the past but I never got around to creating or hosting a website myself. Doing something like that sounded interesting for learning purposes, so why not try it out?
Well, to be honest, I am not really &amp;ldquo;creating&amp;rdquo; the website myself now either because I ended up using Hugo, nor am I actually hosting it myself as I opted for using GitHub Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
